Amemura TV Extra Part 2
Guests are Kanami Tsujino aka Kanamin from the 6-member idol unit Chotokimeki Advertising Dept.
Kanami Tsujino aka Kanamin and
Haruka Koizumi aka Oharu
What do these two members have in common?
What would happen if we asked them to draw each other's faces?
Amemura TV has started!
Amemura TV is now on YouTube!
Amemura TV Extra Part 2
This is Tsuru, the MC!
Continuing from the first half of today's guests
We have these guests with us today.
Please introduce yourselves.
Lock on your heart!
We're Cho Tokimeki Sendenbu!
Please!
I am super tokimeki blue Tsujino Kanami aka Kanamin
I am super tokimeki pink Koizumi Haruka aka Oharu
Please take care of me!
I was a little bit excited.
You were excited and now slightly inspired!
Thank you.
You look like that.
Thank you very much.
In the second half of the show, we're going to delve more deeply into the characters of the two of you.
First of all, I'd like to go to this corner, which is a staple of Ameblo TV.
The Ameblo TV regular dice talk corner.
Do you want a microphone?
Now, here are the various topics.
Yes, it's a tiny one, isn't it?
It's tiny.
Oh, that's right. If you write with your face, you won't do it, right?
No, no.
Now, I would like to ask each member to talk about what he or she wrote at the end.
I'd like to introduce what I want to eat at the end of my life, what I don't like, what I've been happy about recently, what I want to try in my private life, and what I want to do in the future.
What made you happy recently, what you want to try in your private life, your routine before a stage performance, and what you would do if you had a week off.
I'd like you to tell us what you would do if you had a week off.
Koharu
Well, I'm going to do it.
What do you think, Waru-chan?
Bashaan!
What would you do if you had a week off?
This is me,
I want to go to Miyakojima.
Miyako Island?
In Okinawa.
And, uh, I want to do peepee.
By the way,
Oharu..,
Where are you from, Oharu?
Saitama.
I see. So you're not from a place that's extremely cold?
No, but I went to Okinawa for a photo book a while ago.
I had a lot of fun in Okinawa.
I recently started swimming as a hobby.
Swimming as a hobby
I go to a gym and take personal swimming lessons.
I can't swim at all yet, but I can swim in the water now.
Oh, a little bit.
For the first time in your life, you're 1 or 2 years old.
I'm not saying that I'm finally learning to swim.
I mean, you had swimming lessons, right?
Yes, but there was a swimming test in elementary school.
The record for that was 5 meters.
I see. So you just put your foot down and kicked without taking another stroke.
I see. The record was set by just kicking with your feet
I see.
So you were completely using a hammer.
Yes, it really was.
But I was doing it for physical fitness and to be able to eat more food by swimming,
I started learning to swim, and I am now able to dive and crawl in the water.
That is amazing.
So I want to go to Okinawa and swim.
I want to swim.
Especially swimming.
Oh, but I still can crawl...
And if this is one crawl, then I've only done it about 4 or 5 times.
Well...
I don't know.
It's not when I can swim 25 meters, for example.
So I'll practice more and more, and by the time I go to Okinawa...
I'd like to swim in the Okinawan sea, for example.
And when you get to the point where you can't reach your feet...
There is no other way but to sink.
You can't stay stagnant there.
That's what happens.
You have to go forward where your feet are.
Forward, you mean.
What's that?
Ha-ha-ha.
Man, you're so scary.
I've never met anyone with that level of potential.
I've never seen that level of possibility before.
Oh, in the water...
Can you open your eyes?
Yes, I can.
Oh, that's great.
You can open these.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what I'm going to do now that I'm getting my nails done.
Ha-ha-ha.
You couldn't open your eyes while you were scoring?
Yes.
In the beginning?
I didn't open my eyes, I guess.
I was like, "Oh, no.
And then you were able to open them?
Yes, I did.
I think that might be a great evolution.
I didn't think I could dive.
All the water gets in my nose.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like, "Hoku-ku-nee.
No, that's, uh...
I mean, it's like when you're diving, you just keep breathing out.
So that's why, you know, if you breathe in
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
If you inhale ah ha ha ha
Oh, I didn't even know whether to exhale or inhale in the water anymore, but
Oh, that was the level there.
I don't know what to do
It was a level.
I come from a planet without water
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
No, but that's great!
So you've learned how to enjoy Okinawa.
Yes, that's right.
But for a week?
Yeah.
We'll be floating, you know, floating and hopping around.
Hocus-pocus?
We'll stay at the hotel and relax.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to spend such an elegant holiday.
I'd love to learn more about the process of learning to swim.
How do you hold your breath? You're at the stage where you need to catch your breath? this is it... that's it...
First, you put your hands around like this. Can you swim with fireworks? Let's do the end-up.
You know, I'm the type of guy who's been going to the pool since I got home the other day.
I haven't been home yet, but I've been swimming the crawl for over 25 meters.
I've already done it.
But you're swimming 25 meters now.
I want to dive too. My dream is to go see the treasure.
I see. You mean diving?
I went to the pool because I wanted to dive.
But I haven't been able to go yet.
What a treat!
If you know what's under the water, you'll have a lot of fun.
Why don't you use a submarine?
We could use a submarine or something.
I'm almost done with your story, Mom.
Thank you very much.
Next.
Let's see what's in the vase.
Boom! There it is!
What made you happy recently
What has made you happy lately?
What made you happy recently?
Well, I, Meiko, have my sister's child.
Until now, when Meiko was around
I was embarrassed too, or she didn't talk to me like a big sister or something.
She didn't talk to me like an older sister or something.
She just turned 2 years old, but when I am not around, she calls me "big sister" when she sees me on TV or when she sees pictures of me at home, but she never says it only in front of me.
But the other day, an idol called me big sister for the first time.
So cute!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
It's amazing, isn't it? If your mother's sisters said it, you would be a national idol.
But if they see us on TV, they can tell us apart.
They don't send us their names, but they can tell which one is me,
For example, when one of my members is on TV, her sister is not there.
Like, "Sperry Jelly like Mr. Bing.
That's great! So smart!
It's like they're able to make decisions.
So it's like she's doing a good job of recognizing me.
By the way, do the sisters look alike?
Yes, we do. I've been told we look rather similar.
Well, Nekko, you look a lot like your mother.
So you might be able to find her easily.
That may be so.
Well, that makes me happy.
And she calls you her big sister?
That's right.
I'm asking her to call me big sister.
I have three siblings and I'm the only child.
So I've never been called "big sister.
In all my life.
I see.
I used to call you "big sister" when you called me "big brother.
I'd like to be on the receiving end of that.
I've always wanted to be the one who gets to say it.
So I asked her to call me "big sister.
Teach me! Teach me!
Teach me!
But you've learned to say it out loud, haven't you?
And to your face.
That's great!
I'm so happy to hear that.
All those years of education were worth it.
I've been making him live the courage of love, too.
I've already won more than I thought I could.
That's so nice. Do you see your family often?
Yes, we do.
He's a nice guy to go see.
I'm the kind of guy you can go see, and I'm the kind of guy you can go see.
So I'm glad you'll remember me more from now on.
I'd be happy if they remember me and call me big sister.
That's so great. Little girls are so cute.
So cute and adorable. I totally understand.
I want to hear a few more questions, so let's shake it off one more time.
Second time, Don!
Me too! Me too! There it is! What made me happy recently
I've been happy recently... I've started to buy personalized love items.
Ai-kei Oh!
I was so surprised!
I was so surprised that on the 15th of July, the day we went to Osaka for a tour, I suddenly got a line from my family saying that we were going to get a dog.
What? And then a picture of a 5-month-old T-cup Toodle boy was suddenly sent to our family line.
It was five minutes before the show was about to start.
And then after the show, I was like, "I want to get a dog and stay home. I want to go through all the formalities.
What? What do you mean? I was scared. What do you mean? What do you mean?
What do you mean? And then I come home and there's a dog. It's so nice.
Did your parents buy it? My ex worked hard to save up the money.
And they decided they wanted this dog? That's right.
That's great! It's a new addition to the family, isn't it?
A tiny child and a tiny dog are really healing, aren't they?
We don't get more healing.
That's nice, hearing about all those cute things.
You all are cute, but cute things gather around you.
That's wonderful. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go one more time.
Please.
Second time.
I'd like to try something private.
Is there anything you want to try in your private life?
I would like to try traveling alone.
I've always loved to travel, and I've been on a lot of donut trips.
I've been on Weirdo trips and so on.
But there are times when I don't fit in with some of these people. I have, but we all have to do the work.
I think it's possible to have the courage to go somewhere by yourself, but I always feel like I can't share it with anyone.
But at the same time, I always felt a sense of conflict that it would be lonely to let that time pass without sharing it with anyone.
Now that I'm 25 years old, I think it's time for me to go out on my own.
Where would you like to go?
I'm thinking of building a greeetah in Sendai in a couple of months.
If you try it, please let us know on social networking sites!
So, that was the best token corner, thank you very much!
And now, I'd like to continue with another first foray into the world of the first generation, and I've prepared this section for you!
Here it is, the drawing corner of AMEBRA TV!
Here we go!
This time, we'd like to have a drawing competition between the two of you.
How confident are you in your drawing skills?
Absolutely not!
Many people have already called me a gawk.
I will choose the winner based on my own prejudice.
Good luck!
First of all, I would like to announce the first subject.
The first subject is
Beetles are the most popular summer insects.
Wow, that's a tough one!
I don't know. Beetles.
Isn't it so hard?
People come here in the summer to catch bugs, and you come here in the summer to catch beetles.
Beetles.
Stag beetles and rhinoceros beetles...
I don't get it.
I don't understand the form.
I'll show you what a beetle looks like.
I'll show you what it looks like.
Here is the correct answer.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Actually, the other day, you drew a picture of a chicken.
You drew a picture of a chicken.
I drew a roan of a foot.
It's a measure of my basic drawing ability.
It's an indicator, so it's a beetle, right?
Yes, sir.
How many questions, horse mackerel?
How many questions?
I really don't know.
I'm so sorry, I really don't know.
Still, it's better to keep it simple, right?
No?
It's good. It's good. It's good. It's good.
You should remember...
I've seen them all over the place.
Beetle attached to a tree.
Beetle stuck in a tree.
Okay, five seconds.
Four.
Three.
End.
I would like to make an announcement. First of all, Kanami!
Kanami's horseshoe whip is here! Here you go!
Pow!
Aaaaah! So many feet!
Too many feet?
That's a lot of feet.
Six feet.
Six feet?
Six legs?
It's a little bit like a walkie-talkie,
But, oh, well..,
A horseshoe whip...
Horseshoe whip?
Horseshoe whip...
Horseshoe beetle larvae... like this.
Oh, wow.
But it looks like a horseshoe beetle.
Okay, thank you very much.
Next...
Here's Oharu's horseshoe beetle!
Boom! Boom!
Four legs.
Four? What the...
It's like...
A stinkbug and a spider and some kind of...
I don't know...
I can only see pineapples from the middle.
Awww...
Oharu's beetle whip...
I think they have horns...
Tee...
The correct horns and insects are right here!
Bang!
It has 6 legs!
Oh!
But the body is split from the legs up.
It's literally a point.
Which is also three points.
It's missing one leg, it's missing two feet, and it's missing
Those horns.
Like a note.
This is the way it's struck.
In terms of the number of feet.
The winner is
Kanogi.
Okay, I'll leave it with you.
We have one more subject for you.
The next one is...
I think it will be a test of your creativity.
The next subject is
Each other's face.
Each other's face
Yes, but even if we do this, you can look at me with your stomach.
No, no, no, you want to look at me like this, don't you?
Left chicken.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
No!
Oh, no!
I mean, I'm... I'm...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Five seconds.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
End
Let's start with
Good morning.
I hope you can make an announcement starting today.
Now, here is the portrait of Kanamin that Oharu saw.
Here you go!
Kanamin 1
So cute!
I'm not such a sack!
I'm a sack, aren't I?
I'm a sack!
I'm not this saggy.
The outline looks like the logo of Otafuku Sauce.
The outline is so drawn out.
But the eyes...
It's similar, isn't it?
The eyes, the nose, the nose, the nose...
So if it weren't for this...
It's so smooth here.
I think they're very similar.
So it's just the contour.
Her hair is like a draw comb.
All in the front.
Pitchy.
Against
Pitchy
Let's make a lot of women's introductions to put up quite a meeting, please bar.
What's going on here?
Is this the tool you use to earn your free car?
I've got hair and hands all over the place.
I can peel it off by hand.
I can do it faster.
and add
sentences...
I wanted to express that my face is tiny compared to my hair.
I want to express that and the smallness of the face.
It's a little hard to coach, but...
It's a little hard to coach, but still...
We have a winner!
So, this time we have a tie, one win and one loss.
Uncle Viclo, famous for his cheesecakes!
Another popular item, the rolled pie!
Yay!
Do you know it?
Yes, I know.
We're gonna have to draw them apart, so I'm gonna find out which one you two are!
Oh, my God! Thank you!
That's great!
Look at the pie rolls.
Can I show you something?
They're so cute!
Thank you for everything.
So cute!
Yes, it has Uncle Viclo's sticker on it.
This is delicious.
Woo!
I'm so happy!
Please visit the staff for their famous cheesecake!
They bought it for us!
Have you eaten it?
Not yet.
Not yet?
It's easy.
Please enjoy it.
Thank you.
You're so kind.
And that's why this is the going out section, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, it's time to go now, and it's already early.
Chotoki Mokimeki Sendem will release their new album on December 4th
On December 28th, the end of the year, they will perform a one-man show at the Super Arena, the best venue in Japan!
I'm looking forward to it!
The album and the Super Arena are still a little ways away.
It's the end of the year, so it might be sooner than you think.
I'm going to be even busier towards the end of the year.
I'll try to do it much, much faster.
I'll do my best.
By all means.
I hope you'll check out the post by super excited Sendem!
Thank you very much.
For more information on the latest news from Chotoki Meki Sendem, please check out their official website and SNS.
Please check out our official site and SNS for more updates!
Thank you very much!
Lastly, could you give a message to the audience?
Yes, today was a lot of fun!
Did you all have a good time?
If you are at all interested in Chotokimeki Sentem
Please come and see us live!
I'll be waiting for you!
Hello, this is Oharu.
Thank you for watching today.
We are usually a group of six, and we all have our own unique and interesting personalities, and we are all pretty hungry, aren't we?
I think all six of us are very attractive girls, so please come and see us live,
I hope you will come to see our live performance and like us more and more.
Please check them out.
Thank you very much.
So, today's guests were the two members of Chotoki Mekki Sennenko.
Please come visit us again if you like.
Please do.
So, bye-bye, everyone!